SHAHROZ PERWEZ

I am an experienced professional with diversified experience under Client Servicing, Digital Marketing & managing new business for clients across media and PC industries. A data enthusiast, excellent at combining data with marketing tools & softwares for business & tech solutions for various marketing campaigns.

CONTACT

- +91 8789894145
- ≥ shahrozperwez7@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/shahroz-perwez-939491134/
- https://shahrozperwez.com/

EDUCATION

CSE, BTECH

Sri Krishna Institute of Technology

SKILLS

- HTML & CSS
- DAX
- Data Visualization
- Email Marketing
- Google Analytics
- Google AdWords
- Search Engine Optimization(SEO)
- Project Management
- Business Development

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR ASOCIATE CLIENT RELATIONSHIP

Hash Connect Integrated Services Pvt Ltd | April 2020 - Nov 2021

- Implemented cross-channel tech & marketing campaigns. Responsible for handling B2B and B2C client marketing campaigns, from planning to optimization.
- Managed project deliverables collaborating heavily with our in house developers to deliver high-quality outcomes on time and on budget for clients like ITC & Asus India
- Met and exceeded client expectations leading to clients like Lenovo & Asus India renewing their annual contracts.

BUSINESS DEV & EMAIL MARKETING EXPERT

Hash Connect Integrated Services Pvt Ltd | Aug 2019 - March 2020

- Generated new business and long-term account opportunities through prospecting and cold-calling, resulting in grabbing an account with Lenovo India
- Developed, coordinated and implemented sales strategies that identified and produced new business especially Email marketing for Lenovo's REL & SMB channel
- Designed and deployed comprehensive lifecycle email marketing program for Lenovo's REL & SMB channel using tools like Eloqua & Marketo
- Measured campaign results and worked with the team on a monthly basis to demonstrate ROI for the program and effectiveness of their running campaigns

SALES AND MARKETING OPERATIONS

Quikr India Pvt Ltd | Sep 2018 - June 2019

- Worked on sales proposals and direct mail marketing campaigns.
- Recognized as the Top performer for driving new leads and sales for multiplle campaigns